Please, let's start dating, for real.
You don't have to give me an answer right away.
Don't space out on me.
Ai?
It's weird…
It's like my eyes keep following him…
That's love!
Love… No way!
Then why didn't you spill the beans when he told you his feelings?
Well…
You didn't want your time with Reo to end, right?
You're wrong!
And, anyway, he told me his feelings about "Mai".
I see…
So you, accidentally, fell in love with him?
It's not love!
Absolutely not.
[Ai-Chan's Secret | Episode 2]
[Maid Cafe | Spica]
You've got to be kidding me…
Someone like Reo?
My little sister really became a woman! Should I make red rice to celebrate?
(T/N: The red color of the rice symbolizes happiness and prosperity)
Go die. And then apologize to all the little sisters of the world.
Want some hotel recommendations?
Stop making me repeat myself! I spend the night at Hiroko's!
Hiroko, right…
Pig-headed jerk!
You've killed it. You've killed the mood.
I'm popular as Aiko too, you know!
Don't you want to win? Against the guys?
If it's a game, of course I want to win.
Then lock Aiko away!
This is your greatest weapon.
Customers come to enjoy a dream, like their own little soap bubble.
It's against the rules for you to pop the bubble and end the game.
Is Mai… really that great?
Mai is an angel!
But Aiko is…
Come on! What's your deal? Go over there!
[Maid Cafe | Spica]
So, did you tell Aiko? About us?
No, not yet.
It doesn't seem like the right time.
You seem kind of down today, Mai.
Listen…
What do you think about me?
What do I think?
You're super cute.
- I see...
- Huh?
That makes you depressed? It was a compliment!
Thank you.
All right! Want to play a board game, Master?
Are you waiting for him to text you?
I'm not waiting for it!
Why not text first? Say you want to see him.
Why would I do that?
[Are you free to meet up now? I want to see you]
Want me to lend you some clothes?
Are you sure?
Want to get something to eat?
Man, I'm starving!
I am too.
Let's get grilled meat!
- Noodles!
- Meat!
You'd make a high schooler treat you to meat?
You were the one who invited me, right?
Someone must have forgotten it.
Why not decide what to eat with an impartial game?
Fine by me.
But I won't lose.
I don't know about that.
♫ Just wanna, wanna, wanna, wanna go and take it ♫
- You're really good.
- You think so?
- You like basketball?
- I do.
What about me?
What?
♫ You are suspicion ♫
No fair! You caught me off guard.
Do you see me as a man?
Probably.
I look at you differently than other guys.
[I look at you differently than other guys]
♫ Just wanna, wanna, wanna, wanna go and take it ♫
I did it!
You're fast, Mai.
I couldn't catch up to you at all.
Have you played basketball before?
Were you playing seriously?
Of course.
You're not even breathing hard.
I lost.
I'll treat you to some meat.
I see…
You went easy on me?
No, you won.
You never went easy on me before…
You got sloppy at the end, Aiko.
You only do that to girls you like, huh…
Please
let's start dating, for real.
You didn't just let the girl you like
steal the ball that easily.
The person you fell in love with
is Aiko, the girl you always tease!
I never thought you were such a coward.
This game is over.
I knew it was you.
I knew everything from the start.
Aiko, I…
I thought I was tricking you,
but I was the one being tricked.
No, I wanted to—
Wait. Aiko!
Yep. Perfect!
- Oh!
- Oh, nothing! This is for Aiko.
- It's fine, Stingy!
- Isn't your girlfriend waiting? You should get…
That was surprising…
- Um...
- Whoa!
Is Aiko home?
What's up?
Is the roof leaking?
Aiko's arguing with a boy!
Ai, Ai...
What's with that reaction? Shouldn't you be more surprised?
Ranji, your girlfriend!
Crap! Text me what happens next!
Makes sense. Aiko is around that age, huh?
Yeah, but don't think about making red rice.
She'll kill you.
Aiko, please listen to me.
Don't just come up here without permission!
Why did you reveal the truth in such a rushed way?
I mean, you just changed your hair. Of course I realized it was you.
You knew when you confessed to me?
I did.
I bet you laughed at how stupid I was.
Did you have fun?
I did, but that's—
I wasn't serious about it!
You always tease me,
so I was going to make you fall in love with me and then dump you.
But I lost again.
Bet your satisfied, huh?
What are you talking about?
Just go home! I don't want to see your face!
Right…
Is that so?
[Kafuu High School]
In the beginning, I really was trying to trick him.
But…
when I was with Reo as Mai…
it was really fun.
But I guess it was different for him.
It makes sense.
Just because I put on a wig,
there's no way he'd fall in love with me.
What are you doing? That hurts.
You can cry.
Why would I cry?
When you're so full of love,
tears sometimes slip out.
I told you, I don't love that jerk.
What are you doing?
- Sorry.
- What's up with you, Reo?
Let's go again.
That other girl is not coming to get in the way today?
Ai is not coming in today.
Things are pretty quiet without her here.
All right, take a 10-minute break!
Ms. Oyama, please make me team manager already!
I know I can control them.
I'll need to discuss it with Mr. Koike.
Ms. Oyama, it's my turn to pick up my son today.
I have to head out.
Let's go.
- I like you.
- I'm sorry.
There's already someone I like.
- Got another love confession?
- Shut up. Leave me alone.
But she was so cute.
- Then why don't you date her?
- I can't.
I'm waiting for my destined soul mate.
The person you fell in love with…
is Aiko, the girl you always tease!
You don't wait around for destiny, you reach out and grab it.
Do you have one? A destined soul mate?
Who is it?
I want to quit being a maid.
But it made me so happy to see you being feminine.
You just don't want to look for another part-timer.
What a shame.
I mean, you.
What about me?
You seemed a lot happier than before.
Well, I'll look for a replacement.
But until I find one…
What?!
Come back soon!
I'm home!
Welcome home!
Long time, no see, Mai.
I hoped I could see you here.
He's acting like nothing happened.
I'd prefer it if he made me a laughingstock.
Ai.
I'll go take care of their table. Okay?
Why doesn't the basketball team have a manager?
Mr. Koike is really picky?
I mean, the weekend strength trainings are hell!
It'd be better if a girl was training too, at least.
Kitauchi, come bring snacks to Saturday's training.
Fine, but what do you want to eat?
So you'd like one of my "if there's any leftovers, I'll punish you" omelet rice?
Coming right up!
Would you come too, Mai?
I want you to come.
- Mai is really busy with college and—
- You have weekends off, right?
- But with her job—
- Right, Mai?
You'll come, won't you?
[Kafuu High School]
You should have said no.
That's the 8th time you've said that.
What if the other guys find out about you?
How many times have you asked that?
I'm serious.
I can't back down after he asked me like that.
I worry about how much you hate to lose.
That's just my personality.
Reo invited you knowing you're really Ai.
If anything happens…
Nothing will happen. Well,
if something does happen, that's my punishment for the gamble.
But actually, I'm kind of glad he invited me.
I mean, I even put on clothes like this.
Ai…
I'm pretty stupid, huh?
Good work, guys! We brought some snacks!
- Kitauchi, you're incredible!
- Is that the maid Mai?
She's super cute!
- Just my type.
- Say, which maid cafe is this?
- Spica, by the train station.
- Seriously?
- Let's go next time.
- Yeah, let's go.
We'll get Mai to serve us dessert!
- Whoa!
- Here you go.
Here, have some donuts.
Thanks!
Let's eat!
- Mai is totally adorable.
- I hope Reo introduces her to us!
I didn't think you'd come.
You were the one who told me to come.
You don't usually listen to me.
If the rest of them finds out… things will be hard for me.
I can't stop looking at her.
- Don't do that.
- Why not?
- I'm gonna get her first.
- No way.
I shouldn't have invited you, after all.
Then I'll go home.
Ai— I mean…
Mai!
- What happened?
- What's this about?
Wait! Hold on a second!
I said, wait!
- Let go!
- I won't.
Just listen to me for a second.
Please.
- You said you wished you hadn't—
- I didn't want the other guys ogling you!
You're too pretty!
Do you get what I'm saying?
I don't get it at all!
When I met you at Spica,
I acted like I didn't know you, and then I asked you out.
But I asked you out
because I knew it was you, Aiko.
What's your name?
It wasn't because you were Mai.
I knew you'd go along with the invite to make fun of me.
That's what I thought.
But if it meant spending time with you,
I didn't care what the reason was.
If there was any chance to make you love me,
I didn't care.
Look at me.
I can't.
You said before that you lost,
but really, you won from the very beginning.
You're really good! Say...
Let's join the basketball club together!
I'm Aiko Kasumi.
What's your name?
Because I've...
loved you this whole time, Aiko.
♫ What awaits in this battle of love? ♫
♫ It seems it won't end in a draw ♫
♫ You hated loosing, ♫
♫ So I won't let you go easy on me ♫
♫ I don't wish for anyone to know my secret ♫
Aiko…
Do you love me?
♫ 1on1 ♫
♫ I make you acting like a kid with just a sweet kiss ♫
Tell me.
♫ Only I know this ♫
♫ Rather than touching, we can melt
into one another's embrace ♫
♫ I'll let you get near just to return you like a wave ♫
I love you.
♫ I'll steal you away before anyone gets the chance ♫
♫ Lips to exchange ♫
I love you, Reo.
[Next time]
Mai would be a better match for you.
Are we going to date based on a lie?
Take a look. We've got battle-ready soldiers.
We're twins!
I'll be your girlfriend!
I want to date you, Ai, openly and honestly.
[This drama is a work of fiction]